# Andrew Quinn

Curriculum Vitae

Address: 4929 CSE,2260 Hayward St., Ann Arbor, MI 48105

Phone: 1.630.453.1899 ■ Email: arquinn@umich.edu ■ Web: web.eecs.umich.edu/~arquinn

#### Introduction

I am a computer science researcher interesting in software systems.

My research proposes new tools, frameworks and algorithms to improve software reliability, focusing largely on improving our ability to debug software. In my thesis, I build new cluster-scale systems to accelerate expensive dynamic program analyses such as dynamic information flow tracking and always-on program invariants. I explored automated systems for debugging persistent memory applications and proposed a new software infrastructure for edge computing.

I am a Microsoft Research Fellow and a National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellow.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Michigan	$Ann\ Arbor,\ MI$
Ph.D., Computer Science and Engineering	Sep 2015 - Present
TT ' ', CAT' 1'	4 4 1 147

University of Michigan

M.S., Computer Science and Engineering

Ann Arbor, MI

Sep 2015 - May 2015

Denison University

B.S., Computer Science and B.A., Mathematics

Honors: summa cum laude, Phi Beta Kappa, Deans List

Granville, OH

Aug 2010 - May 2014

#### Fellowships and Awards

# Microsoft Research Fellowship Two year fellowship awarded to nine early-career Ph.D. students National Science Foundation Graduate Student Research Fellowship Three year fellowship awarded for ... John L. Gilpatrick Mathematics Award, Denison University Awarded to the most outstanding senior major in the Math and CS department Ted Barclay Top Five Student Athlete, Denison University Apr 2014

#### Conference Publications

Ian Neal, Ben Reeves, Ben Stoler, **Andrew Quinn**, Youngjin Kwon, Simon Peter and Baris Kasikci Agamotto: How Persistent is your Persistent Memory Application?. To appear in Proceedings of the 2020 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2020. Acceptance Rate: 70/398 = 17.6%

#### Andrew Quinn, Jason Flinn, and Michael Cafarella

Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging. In Proceedings of the 2018 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). October 2018. Acceptance Rate: 47/264 = 17.8%

#### Andrew Quinn, David Devecsery, Peter M. Chen and Jason Flinn

Awarded to the top five student athletes at Denison based on GPA.

JetStream: Cluster-scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries. In Proceedings of the 2016 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2016. Acceptance Rate: 47/267 = 17.6%

# WORKSHOP PUBLICATIONS

#### Matt Furlong, Andrew Quinn, and Jason Flinn

The case for Determinism on the Edge. In 2nd USENIX Workshop on Hot Topics in Edge Computing (HotEdge). July 2019 Acceptance Rate: 22/39 = 56%

#### Andrew Quinn, Michael Cafarella, and Jason Flinn

You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding observability with the OmniTable. In Proceedings of the Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS). May 2019 Acceptance Rate: 30/125 = 24%

#### Presentations

You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding Observability with the OmniTable Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS)	May 2019
Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI)	Oct 2018
JetStream: Cluster-Scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI)	Nov 2016
Power Management for Malleable Job Scheduling Denison University department of Math and Computer Science FaST talk	Apr 2014

#### TEACHING EXPERIENCE

University of Michigan Graduate Student Instructor for Data Structures and Algorithms	$\begin{array}{c} Ann\ Arbor,\ MI\\ {\rm May\ 2019\ -\ Jun\ 2019} \end{array}$
Denison University Computer Science Tutor for Introduction to Computer Science	Granville, OH Jan 2012 - May 2014

#### PROFESSIONAL SERVICE

THOPESSIONAL DERVICE	
External Review Committee Member Architectural Support for Programming Languages and Operating Systems (ASPLOS)	2021
Conference Shadow Program Committee Member European Conference on Computer Systems (EuroSys)	2020
Ph.D. Admissions Committee Member University of Michigan Department of Computer Science and Engineering	2018

Professional Experience	
University of Michigan Graduate Student advised by Dr. Jason Flinn and Dr. Peter Chen	Ann Arbor, MI Sep 2015 - Present
Microsoft Corp. Research Intern mentored by Dr. Suman Nath	$\begin{array}{c} Redmond,\ WA \\ \text{May 2017 - Aug 2017} \end{array}$
International Business Machines (IBM) Software Development Engineer	$\begin{array}{c} Dublin,\ OH\\ \text{Jun}\ 2014\ -\ \text{Aug}\ 2015 \end{array}$
Denison University Research assistant mentored by Dr. Jessen Havill	Granville, OH Aug 2013 - May 2014

## International Business Machines (IBM)

Software Development Engineering Intern

Dublin, OH May 2013 - Aug 2013

#### **Denison University**

Research assistant mentored by Dr. Jessen Havill

Granville, OH May 2012 - Aug 2012

### OUTREACH ACTIVITIES

Discover Engineering, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI Techie Club, Georgian Heights Elementary, Columbus, OH A Call to College, Newark Elementary Schools, Newark, OH

Aug 2019

 $\begin{array}{c} {\rm Aug} \ 2014 - {\rm Aug} \ 2015 \\ {\rm Sep} \ 2012 - {\rm Dec} \ 2013 \end{array}$